<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Animations</string>
    <string name="multiline_stuff">\nIt is that time of the year again, when porota-dim bhaji are replaced by panta-ilish for breakfast, the time when loud and flamboyant processions are not frowned upon but become a part of everyones to-do lists. Dhaka has a reputation for spawning a good number of infected souls. Somehow, festive atmosphere seem to bring out the worst in some folks and they graciously play the role of villains during celebrations. Do not be that jerk. Please.
        \n\n
        <b>Do not cause chaos on the streets.</b> \n So after much anticipation when the big day finally arrives for you to unleash your Bengaliness, you decide to amplify the experience with a noisy bang which is most likely to disrupt the essence of the festival altogether. Do not be that person who collects their friends in their muffler removed car, blaring the latest Bollywood hits [or in any other language for that matter]. Generating mayhem is a socially unacceptable thing to do. Celebrations are meant to be fun for everyone, not torture for some.
        \n\n
        <b>Do not perpetuate ignorance on social media</b>
        \n
        You are ready. You crack your neck sideways and flex your fingers. The moment has finally arrived for you to upload the Noboborsho status which will probably get you around a hundred likes because you have decided to add a nice “Happy New Year” GIF along with it. You type in “ShubhoNoboborsho 2k17!!!!” only to get bombarded by angry reacts. You do not know where you went wrong. Do your research, mate. Often, one might stumble upon keyboard warriors passionately fighting it out on whether the Noboborsho posts should be uploaded at midnight or at dawn. WHY?!?
        \n
        P.S. Checking in at a 5 star hotel, saying your Pahela Baishakh > mine just makes you seem lame.
        \n\n
        <b>Do not be trashy</b>
        \n
        Street food is a big part of Pahela Baishakh celebration. Indulging in gastronomic activities does not mean you should litter the park or streets with ice cream sticks, plastic cups and plates, turning the venue into a landfill.
        \n\n
        <b>DO NOT encourage or participate in harassment</b>
        \n
        If you witness a female being harassed, before taking out your phone to record the incident – so that you could later upload it on the internet, condemning the act and look like a legit social justice warrior – DO TRY AND GATHER PEOPLE TO STOP IT. If your friend is catcalling a girl in a rickshaw all in good humour, please feel free to punch him in the face, all in good humour. If you feel an urge to harass a girl in the crowd, lock yourself up in a bathroom.
        \n\n
    </string>
</resources>
